{
    "id": "93fd445a3a4d43ae9a54f0c8c96c3ddb",
    "title": "Prepositions after particular words and expressions",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "5169afb07d714477bbeba02ec31b6a72",
            "title": "Prepositions After Particular Words And Expressions",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Those glasses belong …………………. the top shelf.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "in",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She was angry ………………… . him for lying to her.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "at",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is not particularly good ……………….. football.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The manager said that he would like to see a big increase ………………….. productivity.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "of",
                        "with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don’t want to spend the rest of my life fighting …………………. the tax office.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "on",
                        "with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was driving carelessly, and crashed ……………… the car in front.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "against",
                        "into",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was quite disappointed ………………….. my results.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "at",
                        "about",
                        "All of the above"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "When the chairman ………………….. the room everybody stopped talking.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "entered",
                        "entered into",
                        "entered at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Our firm has just ………………… an agreement with them.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "entered",
                        "entered with",
                        "entered into"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "You are lacking ……………….. tact.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "at",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}